Alexandra Campbell 1+ (602) 625-2503

AlexandraBrinnCampbell@gmail.com GitHub user killeraliens

website

killeraliens.github.io/alexandra-brinn

Dedicated programmer coming from a background in industrial design and graphics. I love scripting digital experiences for people and can offer a range of both creative and technical skills. Always ready to work with any new tools for the job.

Dev

JavaScript • React • Enzyme • jQuery • HTML5 • CSS/Sass • Bootstrap • Node.js • Ruby on Rails • SQL • PostgreSQL • MVC architecture • OOP • git • GitHub • Heroku

UX & UI

Webflow • Invision • Adobe Creative Suite • Sketch • Figma • Whimsical • Mindnode • AutoCad • user interviews & testing • branding & creative content

Education

May 2019 - Curr

Thinkful. JavaScript, Node Fullstack Engineering Program

Jan - Mar 2019

Le Wagon, London. Ruby on Rails Coding Bootcamp

Feb - Mar 2018

General Assembly 8 week course in UX design

BDES Industrial Design, 2007

Emily Carr University, Vancouver BC

Experience

Apr 2015 - Jul 2018

Burgeon Group | Design Project Manager | instagram @BurgeonGroup

- Managed various projects from start to completion by coordinating amongst stakeholders including clients, designers, and fabrication departments.
- Contributed to spatial design, client communications, and marketing content, as well as executed and presented technical drafting, construction & installation plan documents.

2012 - 2015

Demi Coffee | Owner Operations | instagram @DemiCoffee

- Provided exceptional customer service and niche experience with creative food & beverage offerings in Phoenix AZ.
- Known in the community for our unique space, amazing cold brew, and attention to quality.

2012 - Current

Curiotile

- Iterative 'flatpack' designs in stainless and powdercoat steel, custom displays & storage solutions.
- A personal project which showcases knowledge on process, materials, and design. Images & descriptions available on request.

2009 - 2013

Ah Diós | Freelance Graphics & Branding

- Collaborating with three others in web, film, and UX backgrounds.
- Brand development and various projects in graphic, signage, web, and packaging for Visual+Intent, Cartel Coffee Lab, Request Manufacturing, Sooh Media + .

Projects

Doctors Near Me | killeraliens.github.io/doctors-near-me

Doctors Near Me is an app that locates and displays medical professionals based on your location, insurance plan, or specialty search inputs. This project utilizes OOJS & constructor functions to pull doctor info from highly nested JSON objects, as well as ES 2017 features to sequence multiple API calls for its filter results.

HTML5 • CSS • jQuery • JavaScript • Better Doctor API • Google Maps JavaScript API • Google Geocoding • Reverse Geocoding APIs

Goat's Guide | www.goatsguide.com

Goat's Guide is a heavy metal event & venue database concept as well as an ongoing study in UX design. I am currently reworking this project using React, Express/Node to reduce app loading time, and encourage user participation with the integration of Facebook's Graph API.

Ruby on Rails • HTML-scraping gems • Watir • Nokogiri • background tasks • Sidekiq • Devise gem auth • PostgreSQL database • Heroku

You can find more projects on my website at killeraliens.github.io/alexandra-brinn